http://www.aalas.org/privacy-policy

MembershipEducationCertificationPublicationsNational MeetingPublic OutreachGet InvolvedHomeAbout AALASJoin AALASStoreCalendarCommunityContact
0
RegisterLog In
HomeMembershipMembershipIndividualLifeInstitutionalCommercialAffiliateAffiliateAffiliate MembersGlobal PartnerGlobal PartnerGlobal Partner AffiliatesFrequently Asked QuestionsEducationEducationEducational ResourcesEducational ResourcesAnimal Training TechniquesCompassion Fatigue: Cost of CaringEducational Product UpdatesPhysical Plant Orientation TrainingTechnician Training ShortsTraining GamesWebinars & RecordingsFree Webinar Recordings for MembersWorking Safely with Nonhuman Primates in Biomedical ResearchAALAS Learning LibraryNational MeetingILAMILAMProgram FormatRegistrationCertificationCertificationTechnician CertificationTechnician CertificationRegistryRegistryCE ExamplesRegistry FAQRegistry ParticipantsResourcesTechnician Certification FAQManagement CertificationManagement CertificationEligibility RequirementsCMAR ExamCMAR ExamCMAR Study ResourcesCMAR FAQCMAR CertifiedCEU SubmissionCEU OpportunitiesTechniciansTechniciansNational MeetingTech WeekCTADAAALAC FellowshipSpeakers BureauSpeakers BureauHelpful HintsAnswering Difficult QuestionsPublicationsPublicationsLAS ProLAS ProSelected ArticlesDigital EditionsJAALASJAALASDigital EditionsComparative MedicineComparative MedicineDigital EditionsInformation for AuthorsInformation for AuthorsLAS Pro InfoCM and JAALAS InfoCM and JAALAS InfoManuscript PreparationFigure PreparationManuscript SubmissionManuscript Review and StatusEditorial Review BoardAdvertising OpportunitiesAdvertising OpportunitiesLAS ProJAALASComparative MedicineNational MeetingMailing ListWebsiteNational MeetingNational MeetingGeneral InformationGeneral InformationRegistration2020 Exhibitors and SponsorsFuture MeetingsMeeting ProgramNational Meeting on DemandConference SecurityMeeting FeaturesMeeting FeaturesOpening General SessionSpecial LecturesEducation SessionsAbstract and Topic SubmissionAbstract and Topic SubmissionAbstractsTopicsExhibitingExhibitingRules and RegulationsAdvertise and SponsorAbstract ArchiveAttendance HistoryCode of ConductPublic OutreachPublic OutreachAnimal Research FAQResourcesGet InvolvedGet InvolvedVolunteer OpportunitiesCommitteesAwardsAwardsSubmit a NominationAward DescriptionsAward DescriptionsBrewer AwardGriffin AwardGarvey AwardBhatt AwardCollins AwardTechnician of the Year AwardTechnician Publication AwardCharles River PrizePoster Session AwardsPast Award WinnersBranchesBranchesBranch ListingsResourcesLeadership RequestBranch Speakers BureauCommunitiesCommunitiesOverviewCompMedAnimal ResearcherElectionAbout AALASAbout AALASBoard of TrusteesOverviewMission & EthicsConstitution and BylawsConstitution and BylawsBylaws AmendmentPosition PapersPosition PapersHumane Care and UseAlleviating Pain and DistressScientific Basis for Regulation of Animal Care and UseDetermining Laboratory Animal Housing StandardsStandards for Assessing the Quality of Laboratory RodentsHealth Care for Genetically Altered RodentsInfrastructural Support for Animal-Based ResearchUse of Animals in Precollege EducationAnimal Rights TerrorismHealth Reporting Format for International Transfer of RodentsTransportation Support StatementAALAS Position Statement: Transparency and Animals in ResearchOther ContributionsHistoryHistory50 Years of Lab Animal ScienceTimelinePast PresidentsLeadershipLeadershipBOT Session InfoCommittee InformationLeadership SummitLeadership ResourcesLeadership ResourcesLeadership Meetings-DeadlinesLeadership Nomination-ElectionBOT Minutes ArchiveCareer CenterCalendarCalendarCalendar Event DetailsRegister New EventIACUCIACUCAgencies, Institutes, and AssociationsAgencies, Institutes, and AssociationsAgencies and InstitutesAssociations, Centers, and FoundationsBest PracticesCalendarsIACUC ResourcesIACUC ResourcesAnimal Adoption Forms & PoliciesDatabasesDisaster PreparednessIACUCsLaboratory Animal FacilitiesOccupational Health ProgramsPAM ProgramsPHS AssurancesProtocol FormsPublic OutreachReplacement, Refinement, and ReductionResearch Rigor and ReproducibilityTraining ProgramsVeterinary Verification and ConsultationLaws, Policies, and GuidelinesLaws, Policies, and GuidelinesAssociations and CouncilsCorporationsInternational GovernmentUniversitiesUS GovernmentPublications and JournalsTraining ResourcesTraining ResourcesAnimal Care and Use StaffIACUC Members and StaffGrants for Laboratory Animal ScienceGrants for Laboratory Animal ScienceMissionProgram DescriptionApplicationApplication TutorialApplication TutorialIntroduction to the GLAS ProgramWriting the GLAS ApplicationPerspectives and TipsSections Step-by-StepSections Step-by-StepChecklist Cover PageA. General InformationB. Contact InformationC. Abstract and Hypothesis or GoalsD. ProposalE. Facilities and EquipmentF. BudgetG. Supporting InformationLearn From These ExamplesGLAS Application Review CriteriaA Strategy for SuccessSubmitting Your ApplicationUseful ReferencesTutorial FeedbackGLAS Submission GuidelinesProject Modification Post AwardFinal ReportRecipientsGLAS CitationsMediaDisclaimerCopyrightPrivacy PolicyNewsStoreStoreDetailListShopping CartCheckoutCheckoutOrder CompletePay NowRenewShippingGuest LoginLoginArticlesProfileProfileName & DemographicsDemographicsAddressesAttachmentsMembership DetailsCertifications SummaryDigital Content AccessPurchase HistoryPay Open OrdersReceipt SummaryDonation HistoryManage Credit CardContact InformationEmergency ContactsCommunication PreferencesSaved Credit CardsJoin AALASJoin AALASStep 1User ExistsStep 2Step 4Step 3RegisterRegisterUser ExistsSite SearchContactMembership SearchMembership Search Detail
Home :
Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyWhat information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit the AALAS Home web site anonymously. Other AALAS web sites, such as the AALAS Learning Library web site, may not permit an anonymous visit.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following waysTo personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)To process your transactions To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site featureAALAS may share your AALAS membership information, from which a member may opt out. AALAS does not share AALAS Learning Library user account informationTo send periodic emails (The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.) Note: you have the option to unsubscribe from receiving future emails.To confirm your certification status if requested by a third party.How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via the current version of Transport Security Layer technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.  After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.Do we use cookies?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?AALAS may share your AALAS membership information, from which a member may opt out. AALAS does not share AALAS Learning Library user account information. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your other personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Disclaimer and Copyright sections establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.This policy was last modified on 5/3/18.Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.American Association for Laboratory Animal Science9190 Crestwyn Hills DriveMemphis, TN 38125USAinfo@aalas.org901-754-8620AALAS General Data Protection Regulation PolicyThis AALAS General Data Protection Regulation Policy (''Policy") sets forth AALAS’s Policy with respect to the Processing Personal Data as part of performing under those agreements that deal with Personal Data for which GRPR Regulations (the "Data Protection Law") are applicable. This Policy is effective as of the Implantation Date of the Regulations. This Policy consists of:SECTION 1: PurposeThis Policy relates to AALAS’s Processing of Personal Data and compliance with Data Protection Law (as defined herein).SECTION 2: Definitions"Data Protection Law" means any law, rule, regulation, decree, statute, or other enactment, order, mandate or resolution, applicable to AALAS and its Customers, relating to data security, data protection and/or privacy, including Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to processing of personal data and the free movement of that data ("GDPR"), and any implementing, derivative or related legislation, rule, regulation, and regulatory guidance, as amended, extended, repealed and replaced, or re-enacted."Personal Data" means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person ("Data  Subject"). An identifiable natural  person  is one who can be identified, directly  or indirectly, in particular by referencing an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier, or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural, or social identity of that natural person."Personal Data Breach" means a breach of security leading to the accidental or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure of, or access to Personal Data, whether transmitted, stored, or otherwise Processed."Processing" means any operation or set of operations that is performed on Personal Data, whether or not by automated  means, such as collection,  recording, organization, structuring, storage, adaptation or  alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination, or otherwise  making  available,  alignment  or combination,  restriction,  erasure,  or destruction. "Process" and "Processed" will have a corresponding meaning.SECTION 3: GDPR Requirements(1) With respect to any Agreement for which the Data Protection Law is applicable, AALAS in its capacity as a Data Processor or sub processor of Personal Data under an Agreement with Customer, agrees to the following:Process Personal Data with Agreements from Customer, including with regard to transfers of Personal Data to a third country or an international organization, unless required to do so by European Union or Member State law to which AALAS is subject. In the event of such transfer AALAS will inform Customer of that legal requirement before processing, unless that law prohibits such information on important grounds of public interest,(i) ensure that persons authorized to Process the Personal Data have committed themselves to  confidentiality or  are  under  an  appropriate statutory obligation of confidentiality,(ii) take all measures required in accordance with good industry practice and by Data Protection Law relating to data security (including pursuant to Article 32 of the GDPR),(iii) not-engage another party to Process Personal Data without prior written disclosure by AALAS,(iv) taking into account the nature of the Processing, assist Customer by appropriate technical and organizational measures, insofar as this is possible, for the fulfillment of AALAS’s and Customer’s obligation to respond to requests for exercising the Data Subject's rights laid down in Data Protection Law (including Chapter Ill of the GDPR),(v) with respect to any Agreement, AALAS will assist Customer in ensuring compliance with data security, Personal Data Breach, data protection impact assessments, and engaging in other consultations, pursuant to Data Protection Law,(vi) at the choice of Customer, promptly delete or return all the Personal Data to Customer after the end of the provision of Services under any Agreement relating to Processing, and delete existing  copies unless European Union or Member State law requires storage of Personal Data,(vii) comply with all audit requirements of the Data Protection Law to demonstrate compliance with Data Protection Law (including the obligations laid down in Article 28 of the GDPR) and allow for and contribute to audits, including inspections, conducted by Customer or another auditor if mandated by the Data Protection Law, and(viii) inform  Customer, in AALAS’s opinion, that an instruction infringes Data Protection Law.(2) The subject matter of the Processing, including the Processing operations carried out by AALAS on behalf of Customer and Customer's Processing instructions for AALAS, may be described in statement of work, Customer purchase order or a written agreement signed by the parties' authorized representatives.(3) AALAS will notify Customer without undue delay upon becoming aware of a Personal Data Breach.(4) Where in AALAS’s opinion Customer faces an actual or potential claim arising out of or related to violation of any Data Protection Law (e.g., Article 82 of the GDPR) concerning AALAS’s Services, AALAS will assist in providing all materials and information requested by Customer that is relevant to the defense of such claim and the underlying circumstances concerning the claim.Please direct inquires toAALAS9190 Crestwyn Hills DriveMemphis, TN 38125901-754-8620Fax: 901-753-0046info@aalas.org
AALASAmerican Association for Laboratory Animal Science9190 Crestwyn Hills Dr.Memphis, TN 38125-8538T: (901) 754-8620F: (901) 753-0046info@aalas.orgcommunity.aalas.org
Connect with us:
Privacy PolicyCopyrightDisclaimer©2012-2020 AALAS. All rights reserved.AALAS FoundationACEAdvertisingAwardsBranchesBuyers GuideCareer CenterCEU RegistryCommunitiesGrantsIACUCLeadershipNewsTechniciansAALAS is an association of professionals that advances responsible laboratory animal care and use to benefit people and animals.
